MMD Touhou
Modeler: Montecore, OrientalCrimsonMMD
Copyright: ZUN (Team Shanghai Alice)

---Terms of Use---
-You don't have to ask for permission to use this.
-You may edit.
-Don't use commercially.
-Don't redistribute, even if you edit.
-Don't claim as yours. (must credit Montecore)

-----------------------------------------------------------

MMD東方
モデリング：モンテコア, OrientalCrimsonMMD
Copyright  ：上海アリス幻樂団　ZUN氏

ーーー利用規約ーーー
- このモデルを使用する際に、許可を取る必要はありません。
- このモデルは編集することができます。
- このモデルは商用利用不可です。
- このモデルを再配布しないでください。
- 著者を明記しなければなりません。 (モンテコア、OrientalCrimsonMMD)